-Oh, we really need a strike here.
-I know.
(Leonard:)-Take your time and concentrate.
-Leonard, stop pressuring me.
(Leonard:)-I'm not pressuring you.
-You are. Just back off.
(Leonard:)Okay. I'm sorry. I'll shut up.
(Penny:)I didn't mean shut up.
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Leonard:)Just tell me what to do and I'll do it.
[SIGHS]
(Penny:)No. This isn't fair to you, Leonard.
I'm sorry.
Wait, where are you going?
Penny, come back.
(Sheldon:)I'll get you ice cream.
(Leonard:)-No, let her go.
-Are you insane?
(Sheldon:)If she leaves, it's over.
(Leonard:)Pretty sure it's already over.
WIL:
Tough luck, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)You did this, didn't you?
Do you think I would break up a couple
just to win a bowling match?
(Sheldon:)-No, I suppose not.
-Good. Keep thinking that.
(Stuart:)Wheaton....
Mm-hm. Mm-hm. Yep.
(Stuart:)I'm telling you, the Match.com chicks
are much looser than on eHarmony.
Oh. You know, I gotta call you back.
I won a bet and it's time to collect.
(Raj:)I don't know about you,
but I feel empowered.